Wh-Why do you hate Lady Tiararose so?
Icilla is sad.
That makes us sad, too.
Let's go bully that Tiararose lady
who took her true love from her!
Yeah!
Is it because I have feelings
for Prince Aquasteed?
Don't you dare...
let the fact that you have
the fairies' blessing
and were able to come here
get to your head!
I-I'm very sorry!
Incidentally, Icilla...
Are you familiar with what
goes on around Tiararose?
W-Well, somewhat...
Then are you aware of
Claire's current circumstances?
Claire?
I-I'm sorry. I don't know who that is.
What? After I opened the path
for you to come here?
Enough. Leave me.
He said he would come
and have tea with me...
If I just use this...
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Whisper That You Love Me
So you were able to meet
the Sea Fairy King,
but you were immediately sent away?
Y-Yes.
I couldn't give up so soon,
so I dove down several more times...
but I was not allowed near
the Fairy King's shrine again.
Please try not to feel so bad.
The cookies really aren't that important.
Thank you.
I'll see if I can sort this out by my—
Claire?
I came to visit.
King Claire!
King... Claire?
What, you're just ignoring me?
Keith!
I heard that you'd been having
tea with Claire recently.
It's been a while, Tiara.
I brought you a lovely gift today.
It's coral tea.
You can make tea from coral?
You're the Sky Fairy King,
yet you brought coral tea?
That's right. It's my favorite.
I did get it from Pearl, though.
But it's good, so I'm sharing it.
Pearl?
It has the fragrance of the sea
and sweet flowers.
Isn't it lovely?
Tiara is my wife.
Don't get too close to her.
Oh, Aquasteed, you're no fun at all.
You'd better keep a tight
hold on her, or I'll take her.
Keith! I only have eyes for Prince Aqua!
Same goes for me.
You really are head-over-heels
for each other.
I envy that.
That's...
I thought I might get to see you
if I used coral tea.
King Claire, who is that?
Oh, right. You two haven't
met her yet, have you?
This is Pearl, the Sea Fairy King.
What are you so angry about, Pearl?
Come, now.
You need to return their greeting.
Do not give me orders!
Just look at you,
a man dressing that way!
Pearl...
What? King Claire is a man?
I should expect no less
of the fairy kings.
They're all such unique individuals!
I can't believe all three of them
are here at once!
Claire, you fool!
Pearl said she hated men,
so I started dressing like this in hopes
that we could be friends.
You favor Pearl that much?
But surely just dressing like a woman
won't make her like you.
I know, but it was
the only way I could think of.
King Claire...
Shh, Tiara.
We humans mustn't try to interfere
in the fairy kings' affairs carelessly.
But...
I'm sure his idea that
she hates him is a mistake.
I'll feel so bad for them
if their misunderstanding continues.
Also, if Keith knew that,
he should've said so!
But I won't give up.
I'll just keep closing the distance
between Pearl and me little by little.
Oh, yeah? Good luck with that.
Oh, I know. Maybe
I'll give her some sort of gift.
Would you mind going shopping
with me sometime soon?
I don't know what would
make a good gift for a girl.
If you think I can help, I would love to!
I don't think King Pearl
hates King Claire at all.
I'm almost certain
she actually likes him.
Did seeing me enjoy tea time with
the other kings make King Pearl upset?
That's right!
Y-Y-Y-You're kidding!
The Sea Fairy King came here in person?!
What are you plotting?
Huh?
What was that tea party for?
U-Um...
Trying to win the fairy kings over
with tasty sweets?
You obviously have ulterior motives!
Then would you like to join us
at our next tea party?
Wh-What are you saying?!
As if I would ever have tea
with the likes of you!
I'll invite King Claire, too.
King Claire seemed very eager
to see you again.
As I said—
I know it'll be fun!
You can't invite a fairy king
over for tea so casually!
Know your place!
I'll let this go for today,
but if you make things any worse,
I have some ideas of my own!
King Pearl, I—
Silence! I am the Sea Fairy King!
Do not defy me!
And do not get any closer
to the kings—to Claire!
King Claire...
I'm sorry.
What's the matter?
I can't go with you to choose
a gift for King Pearl.
Why not?
You don't want to anymore?
When choosing a gift
for a woman you like,
I don't think it's wise to go shopping
for it with another woman.
The young maiden in me
would want such a gift to be chosen
personally by the man buying it.
I'm sure she'll be happier
with a gift you chose yourself.
So that's what a maiden's
heart desires, is it?
In that case, I'll try shopping on my own.
Thank you, Tiararose.
Are you looking for a gift?
Yes, that's right.
I was thinking of something
made with coral.
And for the color... I'm not sure...
Red is beautiful,
but the colors of the sky
and sea are lovely, too.
This one is nice. I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
I hope she'll like it.
Oh, goodness! These are adorable!
They'd suit Tiararose perfectly!
Since we've gotten
to be such good friends,
maybe I'll buy matching ones.
Claire...
He looks so happy about this...
The seas are getting rough?
Pearl, what's wrong?
What in the world is going on?
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
I must inform Prince Aquasteed right away!
Icilla!
Icilla, the king is angry!
The fairy king? What has happened?
She's angry! She's angry!
She's super angry!
Hey. Don't go acting on your own.
King!
Hmph. I dislike
the woman called Tiararose.
She has some nerve leading Claire on.
Lady Tiararose did that?
Icilla, you must take Aquasteed
away from Tiararose.
What?
What is this?
The secret elixir of the sea.
Secret elixir?
Yes. If you add one
drop of your blood to it
and make Aquasteed drink it,
his heart will belong to you.
His heart? Then this is...
a love potion?
So with this...
I could make Prince Aquasteed love me?
I know it's wrong.
I can't just toy with Prince Aquasteed's
feelings however I please.
But...
Pearl!
Claire!
What in the world is wrong?
I have nothing to say to you!
Wait!
Oh, darn it. She just
won't listen to a word I say.
Lift your head, Icilla Pearllant.
Tell me what has happened to Pearl.
King Pearl said that Lady Tiararose
is leading you on.
Leading me on? That's ridiculous.
U-Um...
Just what does Pearl think
is happening here?
It's clear how much Tiararose
and Aquasteed love each other.
Blessings of the forest, please
share a bit of your power with me.
Since I've received Keith's blessing,
my magic has made a lot of progress.
Putting my magic into my sweets
seems to make them taste even better.
Oh, that's very cute!
It's Prince Aquasteed, isn't it?
That's right. I thought
I'd make iced cookies of everyone.
Next is King Claire.
I wonder if he was able to buy that gift.
K-King Pearl?!
You... That...
Is that meant to be in Claire's image?!
Th-This is...
After all those times I warned you,
you mean to continue leading him on?!
You're wrong! I'm making
cookies of everyone!
I didn't just make one
for King Claire alone!
Well, just enjoy your fun
while you still can.
What?
Soon you will feel
the same pain that I feel.
Lady Tiararose...
The sea remains murky and black.
It looks like we have no choice
but to see Claire and the Sea Fairy King.
Elliot and I will go on horseback.
Tiara and Lady Icilla,
please follow us in a carriage.
I'll make arrangements right away.
Soon you will feel
the same pain that I feel.
What did she mean by that?
Prince Aqua...
It'll be all right.
Yes.
Lady Icilla, is something wrong?
N-No...
Let's have tea!
At a time like this, the best thing
to do is calm our minds.
I'll help you.
Water of life, come forth.
Wow! Thank you, Lady Icilla!
Not at all. This is really
the only way I can be of use.
That isn't true.
Lady Icilla, you are
a fine caretaker of the seas.
No, I'm not.
I couldn't stop the sea
from turning black.
But you went down to the ocean floor
hoping to do something
about it, didn't you?
Even when the Sea Fairy King stopped you,
you tried over and over.
You didn't give up.
In that same way, you have
done everything in your power
for both the seas and the kingdom
for all these years.
I know that well.
Prince Aquasteed...
Here you are, Prince Aqua.
Thank you, Tiara.
If you add one drop of your blood to it
and make Aquasteed drink it,
his heart will belong to you.
Prince...
Prince Aquasteed...
Prince Aquasteed!
Thank you.
Lady Icilla, eat with us.
Lady Tiararose...
I'll think about what we can do next, too.
Let's try our hardest together.
No! Please don't drink that tea,
Prince Aquasteed!
L-Lady Icilla?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry... I... I...
I put the secret elixir of the sea
in Prince Aquasteed's tea!
Secret elixir of the sea?
I-It's a love potion.
What?
I never would have imagined...
Don't cry, Icilla.
Low and sweet... The same
voice he uses to talk to me...
Icilla.
Prince Aquasteed!
You're going to the sea, correct?
That's right.
I'll take Icilla there first.
The sea fairies love Icilla,
so she should go with me.
P-Prince Aqua...
Oh. Tiara, you can wait here
at the castle if you want.
No. It's because of the drug.
The usual Prince Aqua would never...
Come,
Icilla.
No! Please!
Don't touch anyone but me!
Prince Aquasteed...
How long will the gods keep
putting me through these trials?
Stop! Look at me!
Prince Aqua!
My Beautiful Lady
Tiara, you taught me what
a joy it is to love.
I must convey these feelings now...
to you, one who is like a flower.